<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="console-application">
  <id>org.kde.kdesrc-build</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>kdesrc-build</name>
  <summary>Tool to allow you to easily build KDE software from its source repositories</summary>
  <description>
    <p>kdesrc-build is a tool to allow you to easily build KDE from its source repositories.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
    <li>Will automatically checkout and update the KDE source code from its source repository. Both Subversion and git repository types are supported.</li>
    <li>Integrates with the KDE source code infrastructure to automatically build modules in the required order, and using the appropriate branch.</li>
    <li>Easily supports building specific branches, tags, or even revisions of a module (or all of KDE software).</li>
    <li>Supports many build systems. It's even possible to build many non-KDE software projects in a pinch (for instance, CMake can be built from its own git sources if your distribution does not have CMake packages).</li>
    <li>Supports speedy initial checkouts of modules (KDE Git projects only) by using the snapshots already available on the KDE project network.
    <li>Supports a "dry run" mode (the --pretend) option so that you can experiment with different settings non-destructively.</li>
    <li>kdesrc-build can download modules (both initial checkout and updates) even while building modules that have already been updated.</li>
    <li>kdesrc-build supports uninstalling modules (manually, or prior to installing an already-installed module) in order to keep the install directory clean. Note that this feature requires CMake support and is still experimental.</li>
    <li>kdesrc-build logs everything for easy perusal later, that way you can determine why things went wrong if a build fails. kdesrc-build automatically creates symlinks for easy access to the last log (log/latest).
    color-coding of the output (which can be turned off).</li>
    <li>Has support for building the Qt Project's Qt library, which is a prerequisite for KDE software.
    kdesrc-build is very customizable. You can control most options down to a module-by-module basis if you so desire, including configure-flags, CMake flags, and your C++ flags during compilation. Instead of trying to remember what configure line you used, you can set it once and forget it.</li>
    <li>Extensive documentation. Feel free to let me know if you need something explained (e-mail address at bottom), or contact the kde-devel mailing list.</li>
    <li>A detailed sample configuration file is included, usually you can just copy it to ~/.kdesrc-buildrc and be done with it.</li>
    <li>Much more!</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://kdesrc-build.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kdesrc-build</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kdesrc-build</url>
  <provides>
    <binary>kdesrc-build</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>Development</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">kdesrc-build</icon>
</component>
